-[THEODNEY] Name: Tsav.
-[TSAV] That's me!
No surname.
Known as the "Man-Eating Ghoul."
Yeah, that whole
codename business
is pretty typical for assassins
of the Gwen Mohsa.
[THEODNEY] You had
eight kills in one month.
That's rather disturbing.
[TSAV] Nah, you've got
your facts twisted.
I'm honest to a fault,
so I'll let you in on something.
It was actually 12!
That's a lot more.
-[Theodney exclaims]
-You see,
I'm so darn truthful
I'm basically a pushover!
Guess that's why I'm always
drawin' the short straw.
[THEODNEY]
You killed all those people,
yet you feel no remorse
whatsoever?
Aw, shit, I'm sorry, man.
Is this one of those
"right and wrong" things?
I'm not great at all that
philosophical morality junk.
Although, it feels
sort of crappy
to have to kill someone I like,
but everything beyond that
is all right by me!
Oh, and none of the Gwen Mohsa
brainwashing really stuck.
It always seemed too ridiculous
to try and take seriously.
We are well aware
of how they operate.
They dispense pain,
drugs, pleasure.
Whatever they have to do
to turn children--
Oh! Are you tryin' to say
I'm some kind of
foretold chosen one?
I won't argue, but that's such
a big responsibility!
[chuckles]
-Have you no fear?
-Mm?
Unless you manage
to get a life sentence,
death awaits you.
Are you not afraid?
Shakin' in my boots,
but I know full well that
fear won't change a thing.
So, why not have a good time
while I can?
That is hardly
a normal reaction.
Can you not envision
your future?
[TSAV] Don't be cruel!
I'm envisioning the hell
out of all that!
Thing is...
I still can't wrap
my head around it.
I mean, aside from
whatever's good for me
-and the people I like...
-[exclaims]
...nothin' else really matters.
[Theodney breathes uneasily]
[Kafzen chuckles]
[KAFZEN] How very fascinating.
Tsav, was it?
What method do you employ
when selecting your next target?
Didn't have one.
Just shot whoever seemed
easy to kill.
Is that a fact?
What about the fellow
named Taldy?
He vanished from
the government office
where he worked,
in a mere seventy seconds
in broad daylight.
Was he "easy to kill?"
Technique or whatever
isn't really the hard part.
I doubt there's
anyone I couldn't kill
if I set my mind to it.
See, when I say "easy,"
I mean folks I won't feel bad
about murdering.
And how exactly
do you determine that?
Well, I guess you can
chalk it up to gut instinct.
They just seemed
easy to kill, you know?
[KAFZEN] Instinct. Yes, I see.
[KAFZEN] Magnificent.
Anyhow, it seems death
is too good for you.
[TSAV] Uh?
[Tsav breathes shakily]
[TSAV] A sentence
worse than death?
Correct.
You are sentenced to be a hero.
Please, no!
This can't be right!
That penalty--
But it is right.
[chuckles]
There will be no sweet release
of death for you.
[♪ opening theme song playing]
[birds chirping]
[TSAV] Don't you see?
I'm essentially a total pushover
when you think about it.
The more I look at a target,
the more I think,
"Whoa, I can't kill this guy!
He's got a wife
and kiddos at home!"
I'm too nice for my own good.
So...
He's a rather unusual hero.
Numerous deaths
have failed to change him.
I just wish he'd stop
repeating that story.
[TSAV] So I'd mess up
some other guy's face
and bring him back
with me instead.
-I'm a big softie--
-[XYLO] Tsav.
Enough already.
[Tsav laughs]
Sorry 'bout that, bro!
Was I talkin'
your ear off again?
Can we please put a muzzle
on this guy already?
He's gonna keep us up all night
if we have to share
a room with him!
[TSAV] But I can't stand it
when it gets too quiet,
you know?
I'm traumatized!
'Cause I have
a woefully tragic past.
What, with all the torture
that was part
of my assassin training,
they'd toss me
in a dungeon and--
Be quiet.
That's your last warning.
You had to go
and make him angry.
Aw, shit! Sorry, bro!
Dotta, say you're sorry, too!
-[DOTTA] Huh? Why should I?
-[Xylo sighs]
[DOTTA] This is why I hate you,
'cause you completely lack
perspective!
[TSAV] Now, now.
You've gotta learn
to take a joke, Dotta!
Stress is bad for your health.
[monsters grunting]
[monster growls]
They're advancing swiftly.
At this rate,
they'll most likely arrive
by tonight.
[Kivia gasps]
[KIVIA] Um, agreed.
I almost hate to ask,
but how many knights
are staying?
About fifty.
I would trust each one of them
with my life.
That's not nearly enough.
Even with the prisoners
Venetim rounded up
from Milnid Jail.
How'd he get them? Bribery?
Of course,
"they're all on death row,
so do whatever you want
with 'em."
[chuckles] The universal
treatment for prisoners.
Hey! Over there!
Looks like some faerie scouts.
No kidding.
Let me see.
Hmm...
It looks like an ugly dog.
My bet, it's a cir sith.
He can see it from here?
The man's vision
is absolutely inhuman.
Tsav, you got it?
I guess we'll soon find out.
Just one thing.
Swear you won't kill me
if I miss.
He has a Verkle Corp Daisy?
Better.
His Majesty tuned it
for long-range sniping.
Are you sure we wanna
go through with this?
If he's in a pack,
his buddies--
-[XYLO] Shut up and shoot.
-[Tsav gasps]
[Tsav grunts]
If you say so.
I did it!
That's a bullseye, people!
More. Incoming.
-I'm on it.
-[shoots]
[KIVIA] Can we truly
trust them with this?
[XYLO] They're effective
as they are obnoxious.
They'll get it done.
Tsav, in particular,
has never missed a shot
as far as I'm aware.
Anyway, we had better go
and set the trap.
-[Kivia sighs]
-[DOTTA] Keep going,
-there are more.
-[XYLO] What's wrong?
You aren't giving up
even in this situation?
Someone wants us dead
and I don't intend
to give them the satisfaction.
Besides...
there's that nonsense
about her "usefulness."
-A little to the left...
-[KIVIA] I had heard you were
a ruthless man
who imperiled your unit
in an attempt
to climb the ranks.
[chuckles] Which noble family
graced you
with a sense of humor?
I am not a noble.
That's unusual.
Especially from Galtuile.
How is it that you're a captain?
-[DOTTA] Is that a faerie?
-[KIVIA] Hm...
One of the high priests
is my uncle.
Oh, so a top dog
at the Temple, no less.
That's why
I hadn't heard of you.
Bro, we're all done here!
Every last shot hit the target.
You two stay here
and keep watch.
Let's go, Kivia.
-[birds squawking]
-[indistinct chatter]
[KNIGHT 1] Carry it inside!
[KNIGHT 2] We need
more materials here!
[KNIGHT 3]
The captain's ready to head out.
Hurry up!
[MAN] Captain Kivia,
must you stay?
It seems lowly
to watch heroes die.
But I will pray for your safety,
if I must.
I shall also be praying
for your well-being, Kivia.
[MAN] Pelmerry,
stay close to me.
That man is a goddess killer.
[XYLO] Bastard.
[PELMERRY] Thank you, Hord.
I will comply.
[Xylo grunts]
Tell me, for I wish to know.
Was I useful in my role?
You were perfect.
Utterly flawless.
I see.
Then will you say those words?
"Well done"?
If you insist.
Well done, Pelmerry.
[HORD] If you'll excuse us.
I take it that was
the ninth goddess?
Correct. The Goddess Pelmerry.
She's pacted
with Hord Clivios,
captain of the Ninth Order.
Do you know him?
I know his family owns
a lot of land
and a vineyard in the south.
There are some people
who would kill
for a cask of their wine.
Although...
what's in there now
is far more bitter than sweet.
[TSAV] Whoa,
that looks dangerous!
So our big plan is to lure
the Demon Lord over here
and then detonate
these barrels?
[XYLO] Right,
we're killing Iblis
with an onslaught of poison.
That nasty poison's
gonna kill us too?
That completely sucks.
Pisses me off, to be honest.
Might even drive me
to kill someone!
[MAN] What?
Say that again,
if you have the guts.
You looking for a fight?
[chuckles]
[man grunts]
All you heroes disgust me.
-Better watch your--
-[grunts] Zofflec!
[Zofflec grunts]
Yeah, all right.
Why do you think
you have to kill someone?
I gotta vent my anger.
You can't tell me you've
never kicked a rock
when you were fired up.
[XYLO] Human beings
aren't rocks.
[TSAV] Whoa!
That's human exceptionalism!
Humans are just one part
of our big wide world!
Not fair to give 'em
special treatment.
[TEORITTA] I have found you
at last, Xylo!
Hey, Goddess!
So did you like
holding down the fort?
Spare me your pleasantries!
Do you realize
that you callously left
without telling me?
Such conduct is unbecoming
of my knight!
I can explain.
Honor demanded
that we fulfill our duty.
Have mercy.
[Teoritta grunts]
Xylo,
did you perchance enjoy
scouting with Kivia?
There's no such thing
as enjoyable scouting.
Goddess Teoritta, have a look.
I found some nice berries
in the forest.
They're ripe and sweet.
[Teoritta grunts]
Picking berries?
In the forest?
Together?
That sounds rather delightful.
-It wasn't!
-Got a map?
-Sure do.
-Duty required that we gather
supplies.
My knight, listen well!
-I observed the Ninth Order...
-Here you go.
-...of the Holy Knights!
-Appreciate it.
-Go on.
-[Teoritta grunts]
How dare you speak
so dismissively!
Listen carefully!
Their goddess received
head pats seven times!
She was praised
with seven separate pats
-within a single day!
-And what are you getting at?
I've not received even
one tiny head pat from you!
I do not expect
a generous seven pats,
but half would suffice! [grunts]
Yet despite my accomplishments,
I have not received
a single pat!
Hmph!
Noted.
-[Teoritta yells]
-[Tsav] Oh.
[TEORITTA] Fie!
Why do you fail to understand?
I'm more concerned
about our lack of soldiers.
The faeries are going
to trample us
-if we don't do something.
-[TEORITTA] Pat my head!
[RAJIT] Captain Kivia,
some strangers
arrived at the back gate.
They say they won't leave
until they see him.
What about?
[insects trilling]
[XYLO] You again?
[FOREMAN]
We caught wind
you were on
an impossible mission here.
We're just some tired miners,
but we've gotta be worth
-somethin', right?
-[MEN] Yeah!
[Xylo sighs]
You do realize what we're
up against, don't you?
We want to help the king
and champions
who saved our lives,
same thing any man worth
his salt would do.
Hate to disappoint,
but we're not royals
or champions.
Go back home to your families.
We're doing this for us as well.
We all hail from these
surrounding villages
and we'll go back
when we're done.
We can't let what happened
in the mines
happen to the fortress, too.
It took our livelihoods,
but it can't have our homes.
Look, I get it,
but you just
got your lives back
and you wanna
go and throw--
[NORGALLE]
My loyal subjects, welcome!
-[MINER] It's him!
-[NORGALLE] You're here at last!
The warriors of my realm!
You are the true heroes
of this day.
Majesty, don't encourage them.
Why ever not, Commander Xylo?
Our forces are depleted,
and in need of brave men.
I'm aware, but still...
-You know what'll happen.
-Of course.
I would never ask them
to throw their lives away,
but I refuse to balk
at a helping hand.
Huh?
I intend to take
these gallant soldiers
under my tutelage.
They'll soon be able to handle
even the most intricate
of sacred seal tuning.
[Xylo grunts]
[NORGALLE] Thanks to these
loyal servants of the crown,
the tides have turned!
Together, we shall
make this fortress
truly impregnable!
Trust me.
We shall snatch victory
from the jaws of defeat!
[ALL] Yes, Majesty!
[NORGALLE] Follow me!
Our work demands
we begin at once!
[MINERS] Hail the king!
Hail the king!
-Hail the king!
-[Xylo sighs]
Hail the king!
Hail the king! Hail the king!
[VENETIM] Not bad.
Seems everything's going
according to plan.
By the way, Xylo,
what exactly is the plan?
[Xylo sighs]
Tatsuya seals
the underground passage.
I want 20 of the Order's knights
with him.
[Tatsuya grunts]
[XYLO]
Tsav takes the back gate.
Shoot anyone who comes close.
[TSAV] Oh! My specialty!
[TSAV]
Hold on, where's Dotta?
He has his own mission
to complete.
The miners, they'll guard
the rear by the front gate.
I want them backing up
the Knights.
We've been ordered not to raise
the drawbridge,
so it's dangerous.
Don't push it,
but try to hold
for half the day.
[NORGALLE] We'll work
on tuning the sacred seals.
Hey, Xylo, what are you
planning to do?
Attack it.
[ALL] Uh...
[all laugh]
-That's my bro for you.
-[NORGALLE] Hm.
Listen up.
Weather the faeries' advance
for as long as you can,
that should draw out Iblis.
Before it can make it
to the fortress,
I'll use a trap
we set in advance...
killing it.
That's the only way
we all live.
Our last hope.
[PRISONER 1]
Ugh, give me a damn break!
[PRISONER 2] I'll kill you!
[PRISONER 3]
Don't tell us what to do!
[spits]
Why should we follow the orders
of a pathetic hero like you?
Well, you people are subhuman,
and you're nothing but
a goddess-killing bastard--
-Uh?
-[prisoner screaming]
[screaming continues]
[TSAV] Can you stop trying
to piss off my bro?
'Cause I'm not in the mood
to deal with the blowback.
But why didn't you
shoot me instead?
[TSAV] You wanna know why?
It's because you're a lot bigger
and stronger than that guy is.
So you'll be much more
useful to us. [chuckles]
[prisoner crying]
[TSAV] Uh?
[Tsav grunts]
[Tsav choking]
[XYLO] Tsav, that was
extremely effective,
but don't do it again.
[Tsav coughing]
[breathes deeply]
Oh, now I get it!
I should've killed him--
-[Tsav screams, grunts]
-[XYLO] Wrong answer.
Go use a sacred seal
to stem his bleeding.
[all exclaiming]
[birds chirping]
[XYLO] Well, what do you want?
A sealed letter has arrived
addressed to you, Xylo.
Seems it's from--
Burn it. I'm not reading it.
[VENETIM] Uh...
Um, sure, although you might be
interested to know
that it's from
Frenci Mastibolt.
I assume you've heard
of the Mastibolts.
A family of night-gaunts
from the south.
They want to lend us
some soldiers.
It's a rather generous offer,
and we're in desperate need
of extra manpower, right?
Don't you think--
-[whimpers]
-This conversation's over.
I won't mention it again.
Even though we could really use
2,000 soldiers.
[XYLO] Moving on.
Why aren't Jayce
and Rhyno here yet?
[VENETIM] Jayce replied that
he refuses to overwork Neely,
then threatened to kill me.
And Rhyno ignored my message.
I should know to expect that
from a volunteer hero.
And the mercenaries?
I tried contacting them,
but since we can't pay...
Dotta's out raising money.
Just hope he's back in time.
[NORGALLE] Greetings!
Good morrow, soldiers!
-Be careful and haul it in.
-[Xylo sighs]
[XYLO] We need to
keep them off the front line.
It'll be the end of days
before I make them fight.
[VENETIM] The end of days.
[MINER] Your Majesty,
what do you want us to do next?
[VENETIM]
Xylo, I've got a little
-thought experiment for you.
-[MINER] Right!
What if there really
are people plotting
to put an end to humanity?
What would you do?
-Why ask?
-[objects clattering]
[VENETIM] Do you believe them?
Conspiracy theories?
[Xylo scoffs]
This is pointless.
I'm already aware
of those bullshit articles
you used to write
about Demon Lord worshippers
and coexistence advocates.
You clearly made
the whole thing up.
[VENETIM] I suppose
I can't really blame you
for thinking that.
But say there is a faction
worshiping Demon Lords
or seeking coexistence
with them,
and taking steps to ensure
humanity loses the fight...
Wouldn't it explain
a lot of things, like...
this nonsensical mission
we're on?
♪
If those people truly existed,
they'd have to be
the shittiest scumbags ever.
[monsters growling]
[Xylo grunts]
Iblis is still far away.
[Teoritta gasps]
They have arrived, my knight.
-[horses neighing]
-[XYLO] Coiste bodhars.
The vanguard of the horde.
Here we go.
It begins now.
[horses neighing]
♪
[NORGALLE] The future
of humanity depends
upon today's battle.
We must protect our homeland!
Hold. Men, set!
His Majesty.
I told him to stay
in the back, dammit.
Get ready.
Fire!
[screeching]
[MINER 1]
Activate the barricades!
[MINER 2] On it!
[NORGALLE]
Another job well done.
Your noble efforts
gave us a leg up!
[miners cheering]
Now prepare the next volley!
Ungood.
His Majesty's by the front line.
Hey, Venetim! If somethin'
happens to the king,
-we're all doomed, right?
-They're here! Fire!
[VENETIM] I tried my best
to talk him out of it,
but he wouldn't listen
to reason.
[TSAV] If you can't talk people
outta doin' stupid stuff,
then what good are you?
[VENETIM] Well,
that's an exceptionally
rude thing to say.
[laughs]
[SIENA] The cavalry is here!
We must support Captain Kivia!
Fire!
[KIVIA] Onward! Now,
Thirteenth Order.
Let the battle begin!
[all yelling]
[Kivia yells]
[Kivia grunts]
[all yelling]
[KIVIA] Zofflec!
Cavalry, hurry!
Turn back!
Keep harrying them!
If they get in the fortress,
it's over!
[TEORITTA] Wow.
Their valiant efforts
are rather impressive.
[TSAV] Hey, bro!
What's over there?
[TEORITTA] Uh?
[Xylo gasps]
[TSAV] Isn't that...
[XYLO] Yeah,
I can see them, too.
-[horse neighs]
-[KIVIA] Huh?
[XYLO]
But I still can't believe it.
[ALL] Humans?
[MINER 1] Flaming arrows?
[MINER 2]
The barricade's on fire!
We're in trouble.
[MINER 3]
The sacred seals are ruined!
What now?
[MINER 4] Don't let
the barrels catch fire!
[KNIGHT 1] Second wave incoming!
[KNIGHT 2]
We're grossly outnumbered!
We can't stop that many!
Dammit.
[MINER] The portcullis on
the front gate won't hold!
They're gonna break through!
-[distant yelling]
-[neighing]
If this keeps up,
before that damn Demon Lord
even makes it to the fortress...
[miner whimpering]
-[miner screams]
-[squelching]
[neighs]
[XYLO]...everyone here
will already be dead.